[
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            1,
            2
        ],
        "question": "What are the two matrices resulting from matrix factorization?",
        "answer": "U is a representation of users in some low dimensional space, and V is a representation of items.",
       "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
           2
        ],
       "question": "What is the goal of matrix factorization in recommendation systems?",
       "answer": "to populate the utility matrix by finding similarities between users and items.",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
      {
        "cell_ids": [
          2
         ],
        "question": "What is the formula used to calculate predicted rating in the matrix factorization model?",
        "answer": "$\\mathbf{m_{Twister}} \\cdot \\mathbf{u_{Stanley}} = (1.0 \\cdot -0.2) + (-0.5 \\cdot 1.5) + (0.3 \\cdot -0.1) + (-0.1 \\cdot 0.9)$",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            2
        ],
        "question": "What is the cost function being minimized in the matrix factorization model?",
         "answer": "Mean squared error over the utility matrix.",
        "task":"Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
     {
        "cell_ids": [
             5
         ],
        "question": "What is the shape of the merged book and rating dataframe?",
         "answer": "(20000797, 6)",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
     {
        "cell_ids": [
            5
        ],
        "question": "What are the column names of the combined dataframe?",
        "answer": "movieId, title, genres, userId, rating, timestamp",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
   {
        "cell_ids": [
            7
        ],
        "question": "What is the shape of the embedded matrix after the PCA?",
        "answer": "(4790, 3)",
        "task": "Principal Component Analysis",
        "skill": "Kernel PCA"
    },
        {
        "cell_ids": [
             9
        ],
         "question": "What is the embedding size used in the matrix factorization model?",
        "answer": "8",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
           10
         ],
        "question": "What is the loss function used to train the matrix factorization model?",
        "answer": "MSE",
       "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill":"Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
       "cell_ids": [
            10
        ],
        "question": "What is the evaluation metric used to train the matrix factorization model?",
         "answer": "MAE",
       "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            13
         ],
       "question": "What is the RMSE score of the best model from the GridSearchCV?",
        "answer": "0.930229238035991",
          "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
             15
        ],
        "question": "What are the best parameters obtained from the grid search for SVD model",
        "answer": "{'n_epochs': 5, 'lr_all': 0.005}",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            17
        ],
        "question": "What are the top 9 items recommended to a user after a purchase of Product ID 6117036094 based on collaborative filtering?",
        "answer": "['0733001998', '1304139212', '1304139220', '130414089X', '130414643X', '130414674X', '1304174778', '1304174867', '1304174905']",
         "task":"Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
    }
]